fans in this installment of spring tips
春季小贴士中的粉丝
we're going to look at Cloud Foundry now
我们现在来看Cloud Foundry
cloud fund is an open-source platform
云基金是一个开源平台
it's a mint for a cloud-based
这是基于云的薄荷糖
applications naturally it's a it's
应用程序自然是
optimized for applications in particular
针对特定应用进行了优化
that is to say while there are other
那就是说还有其他
lower level concerns that are present in
存在于较低层次的关注
every application stack these are not as
每个应用程序堆栈都不是
visible as you might expect them to be
可见，正如您所期望的那样
if you've come from lower level
如果您来自较低级别
components like an infrastructure as a
像基础架构这样的组件
service offering something like Amazon
服务提供类似亚马逊的服务
Web Services or Google compute engine or
网络服务或Google计算引擎或
Microsoft Azure etc right these are
Microsoft Azure等，这些是
these services are primarily sort of
这些服务主要是
focused this focused on them now
现在把重点放在他们身上
allowing you to rent and then work with
允许您租用然后与
and maple 8 servers right the the bits
和Maple 8服务器就位了
and and pieces associated with servers
和与服务器相关的部分
so hard drives Rams CPU etcetera those
所以硬盘Rams CPU等
kinds of capacities that you care about
您关心的各种能力
at that low level are certainly there
这么低的水平肯定在那里
but we don't care about them and we
但是我们不在乎他们，我们
deliver the most important thing which
提供最重要的东西
is business value application set of
是的业务价值应用程序集
functionality right so Cloud Foundry
功能正确，因此Cloud Foundry
gives you the ability to automate away a
使您能够自动执行
lot of that lower-level stuff by
很多较低级别的东西
focusing on a specific type of
专注于特定类型的
application online transactional sort of
应用程序在线交易
application my transaction I mean it
应用我的交易我是真的
does requests or replies it's an online
是否要求或回复在线
application and it's a in particular
应用程序，这是一个特别的
it's an application that is stateless so
这是一个无状态的应用程序
of course there can be some state if
当然，如果
there needs to be but that state is
需要存在，但状态是
typically held somewhere else and if you
通常在其他地方举行，如果你
have state a complex state as you would
像您那样将状态设为复杂状态
for example in a custom database then
例如在自定义数据库中
crowdfunding
众筹
isn't the isn't necessarily the easiest
不是，不一定是最简单的
or most most correct way to to run that
或最正确的运行方式
kind of application if you want a if
如果您想要
you're trying to build a stateless web
您正在尝试建立无状态的网站
application or service or something that
应用程序或服务或其他
handles requests that intern talks to a
处理实习生与
stateful service that's a great fit for
有状态服务，非常适合
cloud family but you know CloudFront
云家庭，但您知道CloudFront
itself is not optimized for running
本身并未针对运行进行优化
databases it's optimized for running
为运行而优化的数据库
applications and there are ways to
应用程序，并且有方法可以
connect services backing services things
连接服务支持服务事物
that hold state like message queues and
保持状态，例如消息队列和
databases and caches and and so on into
数据库和缓存等
cloud funding now Cloud Foundry is open
云资金现已开放Cloud Foundry已开放
tor so like I say it's a it's a part of
就像我说的，这是它的一部分
a foundation in fact it's managed by the
一个基金会实际上是由
Linux
的Linux
Foundation the very same foundation that
基础与
manages their Linux open-source project
管理他们的Linux开源项目
it has a lot of different contributors
它有很多不同的贡献者
from all around the ecosystem all around
来自各地的生态系统
the industry including HP for example I
包括惠普在内的行业
think Baidu's in there certainly pivotal
认为百度在那里肯定是关键的
is in there iBM is in there so these are
iBM在里面，所以这些是
companies that have all taken the
都采取了
original open source Cloud Foundry code
原始的开源Cloud Foundry代码
which those of us have pivotal and
我们这些人具有关键性
previously at VMware developed and
以前在VMware开发并
they've you know joined in the
他们知道你加入了
initiative they joined in the effort
他们加入了倡议
some of these companies have their own
其中一些公司有自己的
cloud foundry offering right they have
云铸造厂提供他们拥有的权利
their own implementation that they they
他们自己的实现，他们
package and ship and sell until and so
包装运输并销售至
so pivotal the company for which I work
对我工作的公司至关重要
of course has its own distribution
当然有自己的分布
called pivotal Cloud Foundry the the
称为关键Cloud Foundry
distribution that particular
分配那个特殊的
distribution is a on-premise offering
分发是本地服务
that is to say you get the box and the
那就是说你得到盒子和
proverbial box obviously it's a download
众所周知的盒子显然是一个下载
but you get the the software license you
但是您获得了软件许可证
get the the bits and you can install it
得到的位，你可以安装它
anywhere you want and you have your own
任何您想要的地方都有自己的
sort of private cloud it can run on
可以运行的私有云
vSphere it can run on OpenStack it can
可以在OpenStack上运行的vSphere
run on Google compute engine it can run
在可以运行的Google计算引擎上运行
on Microsoft Azure it can run on Amazon
在Microsoft Azure上它可以在亚马逊上运行
Web Services etc etc etc so you can
网络服务等等等，因此您可以
deploy it on any of these different
部署在任何这些不同的
infrastructure layers and applications
基础设施层和应用
that are written for Cloud Foundry will
为Cloud Foundry写的
run portably across all these different
可在所有这些不同的地方轻松运行
layers so if you are an organization
分层，因此，如果您是一个组织
that wants to move to the cloud but
想移到云端，但是
maybe you haven't yet made the leap to a
也许您还没有迈向
sort of a public host in a cloud
有点像云中的公共主机
environment then you can install Cloud
环境，然后您可以安装Cloud
Foundry and get this sort of velocity
铸造并获得这种速度
that moving to a cloud environment gives
迁移到云环境中
you in your own local data center and
您在自己的本地数据中心中
then when the time comes for you to move
然后当时间到了
to public cloud you're ready just
到公共云就可以了
install it there understand right it's
将其安装在那里，了解它的正确性
the same platform same everything in
相同的平台
fact you can have you know it's very
其实你可以知道
easy to have hybrid sort of
容易混合
configurations where you have a local
您具有本地配置的配置
private data center sort of clouds and
私有数据中心有点云
publicly hosted clouds as well now the
现在也是公共托管的云
the the thing we're gonna look at today
我们今天要看的东西
is called pivotal web services this is a
被称为关键网络服务，这是一个
hosted implementation of Cloud Foundry
托管Cloud Foundry的实施
it's it is just regular Cloud Foundry
这只是常规的Cloud Foundry
it's deployed on Amazon East so it's
它部署在Amazon East上，因此
running on
继续
services and it's not private right when
服务，这不是私人权利
you get an account on pivotal Web
您在关键网络上获得了一个帐户
Services
服务
it's a multi-tenant environment
这是一个多租户环境
obviously it's secure you know with you
显然，与您一起了解是安全的
know apps aren't supposed to see each
知道应用程序不应该看到每个
other know that but in theory you could
其他人知道，但是理论上你可以
be sharing a computer with some other
与其他人共享一台计算机
application right it's a great place to
正确的应用程序，这是一个绝佳的选择
start your journey with Cloud Foundry I
从Cloud Foundry I开始您的旅程
think because it's right you know it's
思考，因为它是对的，你知道它是
very very um reasonably price it's cheap
非常非常合理的价格很便宜
for for small sized applications and
用于小型应用
reasonably priced
合理的价格
thereafter and it doesn't require you to
之后，它不需要您
to lay down a cluster right lay down a
放下一个集群，放下一个
whole topology you just get an account
整个拓扑您只需一个帐户
and start using it so we're gonna build
并开始使用它，所以我们将建立
a simple application first just a
一个简单的应用程序首先只是
regular spring application a data
常规春季申请数据
centric application I'm going to call
我要打电话给中心应用程序
the CF data demo I'm going to use my
我将要使用的CF数据演示
sequel we'll use the web support rest
续集，我们将使用网络支持
repository support actuator support and
仓库支持执行器支持和
I think that we'll do own JPA so we use
我认为我们将拥有JPA，因此我们使用
JP as well and we'll hit generate give
JP也是如此，我们将点击generate Give
ourselves a new zip file here okay so
给我们自己一个新的zip文件，好吧
what we're going to do is we're gonna
我们要做的是
just store some data in a my sequel
只是将一些数据存储在我的续集中
database and the reason we use my
数据库以及我们使用我的原因
sequels because that's actually one of
续集，因为这实际上是其中之一
the many backing services that we can
我们可以提供的许多支持服务
use on Cloud Foundry so we need to in
在Cloud Foundry上使用，因此我们需要
our application create some data and I
我们的应用程序创建了一些数据，我
think we'll just mend some cats here
认为我们会在这里修补一些猫
right cats are fine so we'll use some
对的猫很好，所以我们会用一些
cats okay an entity okay
猫好了实体好了
private long id id id private string
私人长ID身份证ID私人字符串
reservation name create a constructor
保留名称创建构造函数
generate value
创造价值
create another constructor this one with
创建另一个构造函数
JPA all right there was that and maybe a
JPA好吧，也许是这样
tooth string good and what we want to do
牙线好，我们要做什么
now is want to save some data in the
现在想在其中保存一些数据
database so I'll create a command line
数据库，所以我将创建一个命令行
runner and in the command line runner
运行程序和命令行运行程序
we'll initialize some sample data by
我们将通过以下方式初始化一些示例数据
using the a reservation repository which
使用预订存储库
we're going to create using spring data
我们将使用Spring 数据进行创建
so a reservation repository or our okay
所以预订资料库还是可以的
and then of course hold up the well let
然后当然举起
the ID do the work here okay so there's
ID可以在这里完成工作，所以
this extends JPA repository a four type
这将JPA存储库扩展为四种类型
of cat here we are
猫在这里
there's my mind cat repository for type
我的头脑猫仓库有类型
of cat okay and there we go now what we
猫还可以，现在我们去那里
want to do is inject that into the
想要做的就是将其注入
constructor so there's this and we'll
构造函数，所以有了这个，我们将
save some records into the into the
保存一些记录到
database here we're going to say stream
这里我们要说的数据库流
thought of and Felix Garfield you know
想起了和菲利克斯·加菲尔德，你知道
what some tuppence okay so we'll go
有什么惊喜，所以我们去
through those names and for each name
通过这些名称和每个名称
we'll write a record to the database
我们将记录写入数据库
using our our cat repository here good
在这里使用我们的猫仓库很好
now this is going to run and talk to a
现在这将运行并与
my sequel instance so we need to
我的续集实例，所以我们需要
configure a few things accordingly we're
相应地配置一些东西
going to say spring dot data source
要说的是Spring 点数据源
well first JPA dot database equals my
首先，JPA点数据库等于我的
sequel my there's this and JPA gonna
续集，我有这个，JPA
have it create a schema for us i'm gonna
让它为我们创建一个架构
start up and what one does want to
开始，一个人想要
create when a configure the connection
在配置连接时创建
to our local our local david data source
到我们本地的本地大卫数据源
okay so going to say that we want to
好的，所以我们要说
configure connectivity information in
在中配置连接信息
the
的
fault profile so if there's not another
故障概况，所以如果没有其他
profile specified it'll use this one so
指定的配置文件将使用此配置
here we're gonna say data source dot
这里我们要说数据源点
username your username equals cats and
用户名您的用户名等于cats，
we'll use password is cats as well and
我们也将使用密码为cats，
we'll say that spring dot data source
我们将说Spring 点数据源
dot URL equals JDBC : my sequel : 4/4 /
点URL等于JDBC：我的续集：4/4 /
localhost for - cats question mark use
本地主机--猫问号使用
SSL equals false for now and that should
SSL现在等于false，应该
do that should be the my sequel specific
这样做应该是我的续集特定的
information to talk to the cat stay
与猫呆聊天的信息
based on this node so if we start this
基于这个节点，所以如果我们开始这个
up the only thing we're gonna need is a
我们唯一需要的是
REST API in order for this to be
REST API，以便做到这一点
interesting so we'll go here to our
有趣，所以我们将在这里转到
repository and annotate it accordingly
存储库并相应地对其进行注释
this isn't strictly speaking necessary
严格来说这不是必需的
because we have spring the spring boots
因为我们有 Spring 的 spring boot
started at arrests on the class path and
开始在上课路上被捕，
we've got a public type so let's go
我们有一个公共类型，让我们开始吧
ahead and and kick it off and see what
向前并开始，看看有什么
happens
发生
okay localhost:8080 for such
好的localhost：8080这样的
reservations whoops
保留呼声
seems I forgot to specify the correct
似乎我忘了指定正确的
database there so we'll try again okay
数据库，所以我们会再试一次
now there's our application cats
现在有我们的应用猫
there's our cats so now we've got an
有我们的猫，所以现在我们有一个
application it's up and running it's
应用程序已启动并正在运行
running to the local database we're
运行到我们的本地数据库
ready to go to the cloud right we've got
准备去云端，我们已经
a very simple application I don't want
一个我不需要的非常简单的应用程序
to linger too long but this is a typical
停留太久，但这是典型的
sort of spring good application right
春季的良好应用权
it's using a backing service that is the
它使用的是
same my sequel the application itself is
我的续集同样是应用程序本身
a REST API or a single page and a poor
REST API或单个页面且效果不佳
or even an application with a session
甚至是带有会话的应用程序
state but we'll look at how to cover
状态，但我们将研究如何覆盖
that in another discussion later on
在稍后的另一个讨论中
when we look at spring session but for
当我们看春季会议时，
now we can deploy this so let's go to
现在我们可以部署它，让我们转到
our command line here okay will do maven
我们的命令行在这里行了
- d skip tests clean install CD target
-d跳过测试全新安装CD目标
CF push - P and what we're gonna do now
CF push-P和我们现在要做什么
is we're gonna push this application to
是我们要将此应用程序推送到
the cloud platform now again we there
云平台再次出现
are many different versions of clubs I
我有很多不同版本的俱乐部
mean there's no such thing as the one
就是说没有那种东西
true Cloud Foundry and so I've got a jar
真正的Cloud Foundry，所以我有一个罐子
file here
在这里归档
I want to log in to my cloud finder
我想登录我的云查找器
instance I'm logging into the cloud fund
我正在登录云基金
a running on on wind-up pivotal dyno so
在发条式测功机上运行
normally you're gonna specify when you
通常你会指定你什么时候
do a CF logon you're going to target an
进行CF登录，您将定位到
API endpoint the EPA in point I've
API端点我已经在EPA
already targeted its API dot run up
已经针对其API点运行了
total that IO but if you're using some
总的IO，但如果您使用一些
other cloud if you're or if you're using
如果您正在使用或正在使用其他云
your own cloud it might be you know API
您自己的云，可能是您知道API
that your environment column for example
例如您的环境列
right either way we're gonna target that
无论哪种方式，我们都将目标定位为
in point and I'm gonna log in here I'm
适当的，我要在这里登录
not sent to Kate so put in my email and
没有发送给凯特，所以在我的电子邮件中加上
specify my password and one time once
指定我的密码，一次指定一次
I've done that I'm asked to specify
我已经完成要求我指定
which organisation I'd like to work with
我想与哪个组织合作
and now this is gonna say this is the
现在这是说这是
same way as you can belong to many
就像你可以属于许多人一样
different organizations on github for
github上的不同组织
example I'd uh you don't have to you can
例如，我呃你不必
use one tool and when I went username
使用一种工具，当我使用用户名时
and password into one from multiple
和密码从多个变成一个
organizations inside the
内部组织
the account that your you're using right
您正在使用的帐户是正确的
so I have multiple accounts multiple
所以我有多个帐户
organizations that I belong to on
我所属的组织
pivotal Web Services
关键网络服务
now that done I'm going to specify
现在，我要指定
number two platform engineering and
第二平台工程和
voila I'm logged in I'm logged into this
瞧我已经登录了
space and now spaces are a way of sort
空间，现在空间是一种排序方式
of partitioning off work flows or you
划分工作流程或您
know work environment so you might have
了解工作环境，因此您可能有
development Q&amp;A you might have staging
您可能会进行的开发问答
whatever for a given organization right
对于给定的组织而言是正确的
and this is a great place to to do kind
这是一个做善事的好地方
of isolated testing as well it's a good
隔离测试也很好
place to sort of scope the deployments
部署范围排序的地方
are in the application alright with that
在应用程序中可以
done I have no applications I can
完成我没有可以的应用程序
confirm as much by going to CF apps and
通过转到CF应用程序进行确认，并
I see where that I've got to existing
我知道我要去的地方
applications that are stopped right so
正确停止的应用程序
none of these are working right now
这些都不在工作
they have no instances they're not
他们没有实例，他们不是
taking up any memory they are bound to
占用他们绑定的所有内存
URLs and what I want to do is I want to
URL，我想做的是
push my application but I want to push
推送我的应用程序，但我想推送
it once I have created a data source so
一旦创建了数据源，
I'm gonna do is I'm going to push it but
我要做的是我要推动它，但是
I'm not gonna start it first I'm going
我不会先开始
to say CF mark it well I'm gonna push it
说CF做好标记，我要推动它
but you know I'll push it and start
但你知道我会推动它并开始
after I've Canyon of service actually
在我实际服务峡谷之后
that's what that's probably a better
那可能是一个更好的选择
idea so what we're gonna do is we're
想法，所以我们要做的是
gonna do a CF marketplace we know that I
要去CF市场，我们知道我
need my sequel if I tried to push the
如果我尝试推动
application right now this wouldn't work
应用程序现在这行不通
so what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna go to
所以我要做的就是去
the marketplace here and wait for the
这里的市场，等待
catalog to stream down here from the
目录从这里流下来
hotel now this catalog this marketplace
现在的酒店，这个市场的目录
is just sort of it's just that it's a
只是某种程度上
catalog of different backing services
不同支持服务的目录
that you can use to to enrich the
您可以用来丰富
behavior of your application and there
您的应用程序的行为以及
are many different options here so what
这里有很多不同的选择
I want to do is I want to use a my
我想做的是我想用我的
sequel implementation and so I can use
续集的实现，所以我可以使用
clear DVD I can say that I want to use
清晰的DVD我可以说我想使用
the spark
火花
plan that's the free plan of the clear
计划是明确的免费计划
to be Mike my sequel service and then I
成为迈克的续集，然后我
need to give it a logical name so I want
需要给它一个逻辑名称，所以我想要
to say
说
CF
碳纤维
create cf create - service and that's
创建cf创建-服务，那就是
going to ask me for what information so
要问我什么信息
I'll say spark Claire DB spark and then
我会说火花Claire DB spark然后
I'll give it a logical name here not
我在这里不给它一个逻辑名称
call it my my sequel right so that's
称它为我的续集吧，那是
going to do is it's going to create an
将要做的是创建一个
instance it's actually a go out in
实例实际上是外出
provision a database now these different
现在提供数据库，这些不同
plans you know they don't mean the same
你知道他们不同意的计划
thing across all different services you
所有不同服务中的事物
could have you know these are arbitrary
你能知道这些是任意的吗
definitions arbitrate names for these
定义仲裁这些名称
different services these services are
这些服务是不同的服务
typically on in on pivotal web services
通常在关键Web服务中
that are provided by actual third party
由实际的第三方提供
web services online services that happen
Web服务发生的在线服务
to have an integration with the pivotal
与枢纽融合
Web Services platform so we can't you
Web服务平台，所以我们不能
know we don't control the prices for
知道我们不控制价格
their their offerings right they're just
他们的产品，他们只是
given different labels and the billing
指定不同的标签和帐单
is handled if you if you choose a
如果您选择一个将处理
different plan and that's already just
不同的计划，那已经只是
sort of built into your account now I'm
现在我已经建立到您的帐户中了
gonna hit CF create service clear DB
要打CF创建服务清除数据库
spark my less equal now what I want to
现在激发我的不平等
do is I want to push the application so
我要做的是推送应用程序吗
I'm gonna say CF push minus P and I'm
我会说CF推减P，我就是
going to specify the cat application
将指定cat应用程序
here okay and I'm gonna give it a
好的，我要给它一个
logical name I'm gonna call it CF cats
逻辑名称，我将其称为CF猫
you know data demo and before I do that
你知道数据演示，在我这样做之前
I'm gonna do a dash - no - start and
我要破折号-不-开始
that's going to push the application
这将推动应用程序
into the cloud platform so it's gonna
进入云平台，因此
what's going to happen is it's gonna
将会发生的是
upload that that jar file which is it
上载那个jar文件
just a zip file and it's going to try
只是一个zip文件，它将尝试
and understand what kind of application
并了解什么样的应用
it's being given it's going to run it
被赋予它将要运行它
through a series of tests it's gonna try
通过一系列测试，它将尝试
and figure out what kind of application
找出什么样的应用
it is in this case it'll see it's a jar
在这种情况下，它将看到一个罐子
okay great it's a java application it's
好的，这是一个Java应用程序
got a main method - it's a java
有一个主要方法-这是一个Java
application that can run a main method
可以运行主要方法的应用程序
and it'll it'll then lay down you know
然后它会放下你知道的
it'll it'll do everything it needs to
它会做所有需要做的事
get that application ready to use but
准备好使用该应用程序，但
it's not
不是
like started or kick it off just yes so
喜欢开始或开始就可以了
what we want to do is we want to bind
我们想要做的是我们要绑定
our recently we created recently created
我们最近创建的我们最近创建的
backing service the the my sequel
支持服务是我的续集
instance here to our newly created or
实例到我们新创建的或
newly pushed application so I'm going to
新推的应用程序，所以我要
say bind service and then it's going to
说绑定服务，然后它将
say that we have to bind the app to the
说我们必须将应用程序绑定到
database right so the the app is called
数据库正确，因此该应用被调用
CF caps and I'm going to bind it to my
CF帽，我将其绑定到我的
my sequel
我的续集
f cats demo - my my sequel and what
çF猫演示-我的续集和其他内容
this is going to do is it's gonna create
这将要做的是创建
a a sort of a link if you will the way
一个链接，如果你愿意的话
that services work in cloud funder is
在Cloud Funder中工作的服务是
that the information about how to
关于如何的信息
connect to a backing service is exposed
连接到支持服务已暴露
to the application as environment
作为环境应用
variables and these environment
变量和这些环境
variables are X you know visible to the
变量是您知道对X可见的X
to the application that we're trying to
到我们要尝试的应用程序
use so I'm gonna say we're gonna go
用所以我要说我们要去
ahead and launch the application the
继续并启动应用程序
application will look at the environment
应用程序将查看环境
variables it'll then understand the
变量，然后它将了解
connectivity information that it needs
所需的连接信息
for for the my sequel instance or for
为我的续集实例或
revenue or for for an email server for
收入或用于电子邮件服务器
cash or for whatever is in those
现金或其中的任何现金
environment variables it'll plug them
环境变量将其插入
out and then use those to configure the
然后使用它们来配置
sort of data source or message queue or
某种数据源或消息队列或
or whatever that it's trying to connect
或它试图连接的任何东西
to so this is a nice pattern because it
所以这是一个很好的模式，因为它
means that I can change the application
表示我可以更改应用程序
I can do whatever I want and as long as
我可以做任何我想做的事，只要
I'm able to unpack that configuration
我可以解压缩该配置
that those environment rebels and apply
那些环境造反并适用
it to my my infrastructure my middleware
它到我的基础设施我的中间件
my you know my bindings to data sources
我知道我对数据源的绑定
and so on then then it doesn't matter
这样就没关系了
where I get those environment bolts be
我得到那些环境螺栓的地方
it on my local machine or in the cloud
在我的本地计算机或云中
environment or you know the CI server or
环境，或者您知道CI服务器，或者
whatever and even better since we're
无论如何，甚至更好，因为我们
using spring Springs in an enviable
在令人羡慕的地方使用Spring
place to sort of hide the extra bit of
隐藏的地方
indirection required to support that
需要间接支持
particular site at hand right you can do
您可以在附近的特定网站上做
you can do different kinds of
你可以做不同的
configuration and it's just in the Java
配置，它只是在Java中
spring configuration it's not in your
Spring 的配置，这不在你的
code and then you you can you know your
代码，然后您就可以知道您的
code is none the wiser it doesn't know
代码是它所不知道的明智之举
or care where the data source came from
或关心数据源来自哪里
if it's an embedded data source on a
如果它是一个嵌入式数据源
local machine but it's my sequence since
本地机器，但这是我的顺序，因为
running under Cloud Foundry you know who
在Cloud Foundry下运行，您知道谁
cares okay so what we did was we
很好，所以我们所做的就是
uploaded the application the the
将应用上传
platform is gonna see that it's a java
平台会看到它是一个Java
application like we said it's gonna run
像我们说的它将运行的应用程序
a series of build packs and now these
一系列的构建包，现在这些
build packs are the these are the
构建包是这些
default set of build packs that are
默认的构建包集为
provided in Cloud Foundry and they only
在Cloud Foundry中提供，并且仅
provide you know
提供你知道
they provide just a well-known set of
他们提供了一套著名的
bill packs out of the box for Java for
Java开箱即用的账单包
dotnet for go Ruby
Ruby的dotnet
binary applications PHP applications etc
二进制应用程序PHP应用程序等
Python nodejs but but these are
Python nodejs，但是这些是
ultimately at the end of the day they're
最终在一天结束时
just directories full of scripts and
只是充满脚本的目录和
well-known positions like get executed
被执行等知名职位
in a certain cycle when it's when the
在某个周期内
applications being pushed into the cloud
应用程序被推入云端
we detect which build pack to then
我们检测到要使用的构建包
assign to the application in this case
在这种情况下分配给应用程序
it realizes that it needs to use a Java
它意识到需要使用Java
Villa pack and the drummer bill Peck
Villa Pack和鼓手Bill Peck
then takes the artifact and it downloads
然后拿走工件，然后下载
and lays down a file system that
并放置一个文件系统，
contains everything is required to to
包含所需的一切
run this application of Java spring blue
运行Java Spring Blue的此应用程序
application that file system is going to
文件系统将要转到的应用程序
be automatically created for us
为我们自动创建
brand-new from scratch so there's no
从头开始是全新的，所以没有
sort of crufty state being capped or
某种国家的上限
anything like that this is a mutable
像这样的东西是可变的
infrastructure right the recipe for
基础设施正确的配方
creating that file system is in the
创建该文件系统位于
build pack and if you don't like our
构建包，如果您不喜欢我们的
particular recipe then you can provide a
特定的食谱，那么您可以提供
custom build pack but the benefit of
自定义构建包，但好处
using build packs is that we now have a
使用构建包是我们现在有一个
standardized template for building you
建立您的标准化模板
know an image of something that will run
知道将要运行的图像
a job application and image that will
工作申请和图像
run something that run dotnet for
运行一些运行dotnet的东西
example whatever you want to use that
举例说明您想使用的那个
build pack can do that for you
构建包可以为您做到这一点
once the file system has been created
创建文件系统后
from just you know examining and working
从你知道检查和工作
with your uploaded artifact or your jar
与您上传的工件或罐子一起
frog jar file in this case it will
青蛙罐子文件在这种情况下，它将
create a container and it'll deploy that
创建一个容器并将其部署
container across the cluster and make it
整个集群中的容器并使其
available to traffic and it gave it a
可用于交通，它给了
give it a URL as well so this is the
也给它一个URL，所以这是
default URL that we've been given CF -
我们获得CF的默认网址-
cats demo that's C of apps at i/o if I
如果我将cats演示为I / O应用程序的C
go here and go to res or rather cats you
去这里，去水库或更喜欢你
can see the data is there and it's
可以看到数据在那里
running in a cloud application if I go
如果我在云应用程序中运行
to env in my application seems my
进入我的应用程序似乎
browser plugin isn't working instance
浏览器插件不起作用
index here we go
索引我们去
you can see that it says instance in x
您可以看到它表示x中的实例
equals zero right so I means that
等于零，所以我的意思是
there's one instance of the application
有一个应用程序实例
available for consumption right now now
现在可以消费了
if my capacity if my demand should
如果我的能力，如果我的需求应该
double tomorrow if I if my application
如果我的申请，明天加倍
shows up on on reddit or or you know the
出现在reddit上，或者您知道
old days we talked about slash dot then
以前我们谈论斜线点
I would be able to handle that upgrading
我将能够处理该升级
capacity so what I'm gonna do is I'm
能力，所以我要做的就是
going to scale up I'm gonna say that I
要扩大规模，我会说我
want to say CF scale - I - CF cats demo
想说CF秤-I-CF猫演示
so I'm scaling it to two instances I'm
所以我将其扩展到两个实例
scaling the I count the I parameter to
将I参数I缩放为
two instances I could also scale the
我还可以扩展两个实例
disc I could scale the memory I could do
光盘，我可以扩展内存，我可以做
all sorts of things here but what I'm
这里有各种各样的事情，但我是
actually doing is I'm telling the
其实我是在告诉
platform to take the existing container
拿走现有集装箱的平台
that it's already built for us and then
它已经为我们建立，然后
just cut a new instance of it somewhere
只是在某处剪切了一个新实例
and so if we give it some time here just
所以如果我们给它一些时间
a few seconds it will see it eventually
几秒钟，它将最终看到它
starts a load balance so right now it
开始负载平衡，所以现在
says that we've got on the instance
说我们已经在实例上
index it conserves 0 0 0 1 so there's
索引保存0 0 0 1所以有
our there's our application instance if
如果有我们的应用实例
we keep going 0 0 0 1 etc right so it's
我们继续前进0 0 0 1等等，正确的是
it's going back and forth and it sees
它来来回回，它看到
the updated values it's now no bouncing
更新的值，现在没有反弹
the work across two different nodes and
跨两个不同节点的工作
we can even configure auto scanners so
我们甚至可以配置自动扫描仪
that if there's more traffic than we can
如果流量比我们多
handle
处理
it'll automatically look at for example
它会自动查看例如
the memory and the CPU and so on and
内存和CPU等
scale up based on those metrics now this
现在根据这些指标进行扩展
is one way to interact with the
是与
application we can see that we've got CF
应用程序，我们可以看到我们有CF
services right this shows us the create
正确的服务向我们展示了创造
services that we've created we've got
我们创建的服务
the CF apps and you know we can also see
CF应用程序，您知道我们也可以看到
how easy it is to push an application
推送应用程序有多容易
and so on but sometimes you want to look
等等，但是有时候你想看
at the content look at the data itself
在内容上看数据本身
and a more sort of human friendly way so
还有一种更人性化的方式
we're gonna go to the console on run the
我们要去控制台上运行
pivotal that IO itself and log in and
关键在于IO本身并登录并
we'll see our applications
我们将看到我们的应用程序
good now when you have pivotal web
当您拥有关键网络时，现在好了
services and I'm now logged into my
服务，现在我已登录
account this is a showing me that I've
帐户，这表明我已经
got so many different apps in each of
每个都有很多不同的应用程序
these different organizations I'm going
我要去的这些不同的组织
to choose the right organization here
在这里选择合适的组织
platform engineering and I can see that
平台工程，我可以看到
I've got three applications two of it
我有三个应用程序，其中两个
just stopped one of it's just running
刚刚停止了其中之一正在运行
started up a minute ago it's got a gig
在一分钟前开始了
of ram two instances running I can click
的两个实例的运行我可以单击
on this to get the details the
在此获取详细信息
application I can see the services that
应用程序，我可以看到的服务
I've got you know provision and
我知道您已经准备好了
specified here and the plan you know I
在这里指定和你知道的计划
can change all of this stuff here as
可以在这里更改所有这些东西
well change the settings
好改变设置
maybe rename it whatever I want to do
也许重命名它，无论我想做什么
and and you know there's that as well
而且你也知道
right and of course one of my favorite
对，当然是我最喜欢的之一
views on this is the the sort of
对此的看法是
information that you get in PCF metrics
您在PCF指标中获得的信息
here right so if you click on metrics
在这里正确，因此，如果您单击指标
PCF metrics gives you a real-time sort
PCF指标可为您提供实时排序
of analysis of traffic going into the
分析进入的流量
application it shows the requests the
应用程序显示请求
errors all that kind of stuff and it
错误所有的东西，它
shows you a sort of correlated view of
向您展示了一种与之相关的视图
the logs as well or at the request log
日志还是请求日志
so you get a lot of information just by
这样您就可以获得很多信息
pushing this application you get a built
推动此应用程序，您将获得一个内置的
in dashboard you get a lot of sort of
在仪表板中，您会得到很多
interesting information that you want to
您想要的有趣信息
know about the application the
了解应用程序
containers that are running the
正在运行的容器
application all that stuff is here
应用所有的东西都在这里
automatically provided for you live
自动为您提供现场
right and this is interactive so you can
对，这是交互式的，因此您可以
look and very very small granularity
外观和非常小的粒度
very large ones and so on to get this
非常大的，以此类推
kind of information and this is all just
这类信息而已
by virtue of the fact that we pushed an
由于我们推动了
application that we had just built on
我们刚刚建立的应用程序
startup spring an i/o now one question
启动 Spring 一个I / O现在一个问题
you may be wondering is how does it know
您可能想知道是怎么知道的
to which database it should be writing I
它应该写入哪个数据库
I configured the my sequence on the
我在
local machine and then I see I've pushed
本地机器，然后我看到我已经推
it into a cloud platform and some of
它到一个云平台和一些
these stuff is still working or at least
这些东西仍在工作或至少
it seems to be working and you may be
它似乎正在工作，您可能会
wondering how that's going so what
想知道这是怎么回事
happens is when spring wouldn't rather
发生的是 Spring 不愿
when cut from Macy's an application of a
从梅西百货切下来的时候
type that it recognizes in this case
在这种情况下可以识别的类型
Java it does rewriting if you will it
Java，如果愿意，它会重写
does whatever it can to
尽力做到
we place different kinds of definitions
我们放置不同种类的定义
datasource definitions in the incoming
传入中的数据源定义
artifact in this case you know it
在这种情况下，您知道
replaced it a rather in this case it
在这种情况下，它代替了它
programmatically adds a bean factory
以编程方式添加一个bean工厂
post processor that replaces any spring
取代任何Spring 的后处理器
beans for type of type of data source
用于数据源类型的bean
with one that it creates for us
它为我们创造了一个
automatically that points to the
自动指向
correctly configured my sequence since
正确配置了我的顺序，因为
running in this cloud friendly
在这种云友好环境中运行
environment so this is this works great
环境，所以这是伟大的作品
if you are if you have one my sequel or
如果您是我的续集或
one rabbitmq and it's unambiguous as to
一个rabbitmq，对于
which you know backing service should be
您知道后勤服务应该是
it should be applied or you are
它应该被应用或者你是
connected to but if you have more than
已连接，但如果您有超过
one then it becomes very useful to be
一个然后变得非常有用
able to disambiguate and for this we
能够消除歧义，为此，我们
have the spring cloud connector so if
有Spring 云连接器，所以如果
you go to start spring that IO and you
你去开始 Spring 那个IO和你
look at the connectors these connectors
看一下这些连接器
will provide that extra bit of
将提供额外的
indirection their programmatic sort of
间接地以编程方式
spring Java config friendly way of
Spring Java Config友好的方式
hydrating different data sources and
补充不同的数据源和
RabbitMQ instances and message queues
RabbitMQ实例和消息队列
and whatever and you know caches and so
等等，您知道缓存等等
on and whenever based on the type of
取决于时间和类型
object that you want to use and then
您要使用的对象，然后
pointing it to a backing service by the
将其指向支持服务
service ID name as opposed to hard-coded
服务ID名称，而不是硬编码
user names and passwords and host and so
用户名，密码和主机等
on so with that we have an application
这样我们就有了一个应用
it's in the cloud we can get visibility
在云中，我们可以获得可见性
into what's happening here we've looked
调查这里发生的事情
at how to scale it up and so on now we
在如何扩大规模等等，现在我们
can also look at the logs right so I
也可以看一下日志，所以我
showed you logs there but it's one thing
显示您的日志在那里，但这是一回事
you should appreciate is that they're
你应该欣赏的是，他们是
the logs here are being multiplexed
这里的日志正在多路复用
forests automatic so I can say CF logs
森林自动，所以我可以说CF日志
so there are the logs for the requests
所以有请求的日志
that have been sent into our application
已经发送到我们的应用程序中
we can just tail them like this
我们可以像这样尾巴
okay so if I make some requests here
好吧，如果我在这里提出一些要求
line this up there we can see the
在那里排队，我们可以看到
information being routed through both
信息通过两者路由
instances you know in one log one log
您在一日志中知道的实例一日志
stream you can configure custom kinds of
流，您可以配置自定义种类的
backing services called a syslog drain
支持系统日志流失的服务
and that drain is just a service X that
那个流失只是服务X
speaks the syslog protocol you know from
说出您知道的syslog协议
unix and then accepts the logs that are
Unix，然后接受
being generated from this multiplexer
从此多路复用器生成
this is called the log radiator and it's
这叫做对数辐射器，它是
just another component in Cloud Foundry
只是Cloud Foundry中的另一个组件
if you're using a drain you can you can
如果您正在使用排水管，可以
specify any you know any valid so slug
指定任何您知道有效的子弹
the endpoint like elasticsearch like
端点像elasticsearch这样
paper trail likes blanc etc and this
纸迹喜欢布兰奇等，这
information will just automatically
信息将自动
appear in that backing service for you
出现在您的支持服务中
all right so now we've got an
好吧，现在我们有一个
application in production we've looked
我们在生产中的应用
at how to sort of add a backing service
如何添加支持服务
we looked at how to build an application
我们研究了如何构建应用程序
that can be pushed into the cloud we
可以推入云端
looked at some of the operational tools
看了一些操作工具
and observability tools that you get and
以及您获得的可观察性工具，以及
so I hope you now have an appreciation
所以我希望你现在有所赞赏
for what's possible here I'll there's a
因为这里可能，我会
lot of velocity that you can get by
可以得到的很多速度
using something like a card front and
使用诸如卡片正面之类的东西
this is great because it means that
这很棒，因为这意味着
high-performing organizations that want
想要的高绩效组织
to get to production and want to worry
投入生产并想要担心
about the the most important thing
关于最重要的事情
involved in their organization and the
参与他们的组织和
most important thing in their
他们最重要的事情
organization which is writing software
编写软件的组织
they can focus on just the software in
他们可以只专注于
this case a spring application which is
在这种情况下，Spring 应用是
very very productive and and really not
非常非常有生产力，而且实际上没有
about the sort of the stuff before that
关于那之前的东西
right the the setting up servers and you
正确设置服务器，您
know configuring CPUs and Linux kernels
知道配置CPU和Linux内核
and security and all that stuff right
和安全以及所有这些东西
alright so thank you very much and I
好了，非常感谢你，我
hope you enjoyed this and I will see you
希望你喜欢这个，我会见到你
around
周围
you
您